[Music] It
[Música]
turns out that the faucet answered hui
resulta ser que el grifo contestaba hui
ling because apparently from his
ling porque al parecer según su
perspective things are not as Willy
perspectiva las cosas no son como willy
said
las dijo
in case you didn't see the click I'm not going to
por si no visteis el click no lo voy a
put it here because I didn't expect everything
poner aquí porque no me esperaba todo
today we're going to talk about this again but anyway
hoy vamos a volver a hablar de esto pero
yesterday his video on that subject
bueno ayer su vídeo sobre ese tema
basically at yesterday's event willy
básicamente en el evento de ayer willy
said that he thinks he was a rat he was bad he
soltó que cree era una rata era malo
called it a rat it's not that I think this
llamaba rata no es que creo que este
fact was imposed that he tells of
hecho se impuso que relata machos
absolute free males I don't know that they have
absolutos gratuitos no sé que tengan
something and the two between themselves that I don't know what it was about that he already
algo y los dos entre sí que no sé qué de
knew that Vegeta and
que se tratase que sabía ya que vegeta y
Greg were more vegetables that grow
greg fueron más vegetales que crezcan a
he likes Gres and that he doesn't want to
le cae bien gres y que no quiere nada
put that he knew the move is that he doesn't know
poner eso sabía la movida es que no sabe
that Willy was also in the batch but
que willy también iba en el lote pero
well he called him a rat it's that he is a rat that he
bueno lo llamó rata es que es rata que
made some videos insulting them from
hizo unos vídeos insultándolos a partir
then on it started to have views what a while
de ahí empezó a tener visitas que rato
the first video that the object of having to
el primer vídeo que el objeto de tener
upload videos that I'm not going to
que subir a vídeos que no se lo voy a
anyone I can a video insulting Frank
nadie puedo un vídeo insultando a frank
that if he saw them he would see a thousand people well
que si los vio le veía mil personas pues
suddenly those are what he chose as
de repente esas lo que escogió como
100,000 calling him one-handed I don't know what and
100.000 llamándole manco no sé qué y
how it's okay with him then I think he
cómo que le está bien luego creo que me
did another one to me and after that well it
hizo otro a mí y después de eso pues
started to get a bit
empezó a ser un poco
and the people and the gangs have
and the people and the pandillas han
offended for example here agustín has
ofendido por ejemplo aquí agustín ha
posted this tweet for a while and says that
puesto es un rato este tuit y dice que
willy speaks ill of believing it makes my
willy hable mal de creer me hierve la
blood boil and from greece to two states but not
sangre y de grecia a dos estados pero no
only that but before I have
solamente eso sino que antes tengo aquí
a video here from 2013 that karime found for me
un vídeo del 2013 que me ha encontrado
that it's more likely not karime that
karime que es más probable no karime que
this is the video that willy is referring to
este sea el vídeo al que se refiere
new kids we
willy nuevos chavales dejamos a ir
always leave it in the background because it would have entered the
siempre de fondo porque habría entrado
video what is most adopted in the
al vídeo lo que más adopta en el
extract of the ice that we found was
extracto del hielo que encontramos fue
a video where it said willy I think
un vídeo donde ponía willy creo que
we are talking about a serious 14
estamos hablando de un grave de 14 años
or 13 year old you can't have a small child
o 13 años no se puede un niño pequeño
until you are going to take a child's
hasta que le vas a sacar a un niño
presence from a decade ago a
presencia desde hace una década hace una
decade ago and he was 14 years old and if you throw
década y tenía 14 años y si me echas
helmets things in my face to nothing it's
cascos cosas en cara a mí a la nada es
a decade because I still tell you but
una década por todavía te digo pero
well or a decade ago I was already a thousand
bueno o hace una década yo tenía ya mil
26-27 but he was a little boy and
26-27 pero que era un niño pequeño y
you know what's serious he's not
sabéis qué grave no es mi youtuber
exactly my favorite youtuber but damn
favorito precisamente pero [__] las
things as they are not how he's going to throw it the
cosas como son no como le va a echar es
only thing we found was a video of
lo único que encontramos fue un vídeo de
greve clicking beacon willy and
greve haciendo clic beacon willy y
putting it in the title and putting like
poniéndolo en el título y poniendo como
his voice in a video in one click
su voz en un vídeo en un clic
4 act calm willy guys okay okay I do
4 actuar tranquilo willy tíos vale vale
n't know if it's the real willy or not but it
no sé si será el willy real o no pero me
surprises me that something was known
extraña que se conociera algo
about willy and caribe against this video and
de willy y caribe en contra este vídeo y
what has caught your attention the most is
lo que más os ha llamado la atención
surely the title I'm better than
seguramente es el título soy mejor que
willy rex and that the cable I don't want
willy rex y que el cable no quiero que
the willy rain fanboys to come here
me vengan aquí los fanboys de willy rain
to criticize me and all that but I
está aquí a criticar y todo eso pero
want you to listen to the comment that I
quiero que escuchen el comentario que
hope to explain well because it's a subject
espero explicarme bien porque es un tema
that really pisses me off like
que me toca bastante los huevos como la
people's attitude and order to give my
actitud de la gente y ordenar dar mi
opinion on what I'm going to
opinión sobre el sobre lo que voy a
explain below in many videos
explicar a continuación en muchos vídeos
on youtube for example my rex and the cable
en youtube por ejemplo mi rex y el cable
to the services in general that what
a los servicios en general que lo que
youtube big led a game of the
youtube grandes llevado una partida del
cable quite difficult
cable bastante difícil
let's see with this it matters to you that
vamos a ver con esto importar a ti que
the cable  or that they go to a game
el cable o que se vayan a una partida
that we simply criticize everything and
que simplemente lo criticamos todo y
say the reason activated the cable dude is
décimos motivo activado el cable tío es
valid if I see it a little absurd
válida si es que lo veo un poco absurdo
what will it matter to you that you of the cable
que te importará a ti que te del cable
50 can do whatever comes out of the
50 puede hacerlo lo que le salga de los
balls because then for example stacks
huevos porque luego por ejemplo stacks
that has commented many times a
que lo ha comentado muchas veces un
video that uploaded that was at night
video que subió que estaba por la noche
playing and I don't know
jugando y no sé
for example and people already put themselves in their
por ejemplo y la gente ya se pone en sus
hands and people believe that all the
manos y la gente cree que todas las
games that are taken out for example
partidas que se sacan por ejemplo
let's see that
vamos a ver que soltó un comentario
willy rex made a quite tasty comment yesterday and
bastante gustoso ayer willy rex y
while it is the next race I
mientras es la siguiente carrera os lo
want it I want to put it well if I put
quiero lo quiero poner bueno si yo pongo
willy rex grez right now look there is a
ahora mismo willy rex grez mira hay un
tick tock with 12 million visits
tick tock con 12 millones de visitas
damn the cell the cl the guy
ostia el cell el cl el cabro
1,200,000 visits has seen does not pick me up
1.200.000 visitas ha visto no me coge
to help me give me fame sense
una para ayudarme darme famita sentido
of will and grace I am not even happy
de will y grace no tengo ni contento
because I do not have
porque no tengo
well I hope to have it from grez answering
bueno espero tenerlo de grez contestador
direct uploaded a title but that I did not
directos subió un título pero que no lo
upload it because I forgot to upload it
subí porque se me olvidó a mí subirlo
because I was like that to me  sent in fact I
porque estaba así me lo mandó de hecho
think on the secondary channel if
creo que en el canal secundario si sube
the shorts go up I didn't upload it because I'm an
el short no lo subí porque soy
idiot
[__]
I was already missing the video as I said on
ya me extrañaba vídeo como conté en
instagram neither the subjective thing was I saying
instagram tampoco lo subjetivo decía yo
like with this kid he didn't make me
como con el chaval este no me ha hecho
a type of willy for long he
un tipo del del willy por larga me la ha
made it to me objective that I have lost a million
hecho objetivo que he perdido un millón
visits people look to know like that in
de visitas la gente busca saber así en
5 but well javi oliveira came to look for me
el 5 pero bueno llegó a buscarme javi
five guys
oliveira cinco tíos
and what everyone report it so that they
y lo que todo el mundo reportarlo para
give it to me I had the title he had
que me lo den yo tenía el título tenía
the red and lost anyway he won't see me
el tinto y perdió igualmente no me verá
with the millions of visits I would have
con los millones de visitas hubiera
taken it if it is because that is what it is so
cogido si es porque eso es lo que es tan
little 200 follow you lied schubert and
poquito 200 seguir mentiste schubert y
this is the same well worth it the profile of your
esto igual bueno valerón el perfil de tu
email one million two hundred thousand visits
email un millón doscientas mil visitas
the ibex uncomfortable put in the
el ibex incómodo poner en el equipo de
serious serious uncomfortable team willy rex
grave grave incómoda willy rex
[Music]
[Música]
well today I will upload the answer for sure
bueno hoy subiré la respuesta de seguro
willy and as if you were encouraged to participate
willy y como que te animaste participar
in the grace tournament illusion
en el torneo de gracia ilusión te lo
told you they play like source of embroidery 2
dijo juegan como fuente de bordar 2
literally he doesn't give a damn about all that that was
literalmente se la suda todo eso eso fue
yesterday when I signed willy race for  the
ayer cuando fiché a willy race para el
team, aside from the bad vibes
equipo yo al margen de los malos rollos
or whatever happens, I try to make the
o de lo que pase yo intento hacer el
best team to play alcohol, so of
mejor equipo para jugar al alcohol
course I like to
entonces pues claro pues a mi me gusta
get along with my team and be
llevarme bien con mi equipo y estar
united, the truth is that was the only
unidos que la verdad ese fue el único
moment yesterday, which was at the beginning, which
momento ayer que fue al principio que
was the only moment that I said, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, lio and Willis
fue el único momento que yo dije uy uy
and let's go from that
uy uy uy uy lío y willis y vamos de ese
stick, let's see what I understand, you don't like him,
palo a ver que entiendo no te caiga bien
no, but well, look, for example, I
no pero bueno mira yo por ejemplo me
met him and I had a good time,
encontré con él y yo hice un buen rollo
calamaco man with the graphics and it's
calamaco hombre con el gráficas y está
ending, man, if you're there collaborating, you
acabando tío si estás ahí colaborando
're collaborating, money, bad vibes, not
estáis colaborando pasta de mal rollo no
six points in the same event, you just
seis puntos en el mismo evento acabéis
saw Brett's television, seen that, that
de ver la televisión de brett visto eso
was yesterday when I signed Willy Race
eso fue ayer cuando fiché a willy race
with the team, aside from the bad
con el equipo yo al margen de los malos
vibes or whatever happens, I try to make
rollos o de lo que pase yo intento hacer
the best team to play alcohol, so of
el mejor equipo para jugar al alcohol
course I like to
entonces pues claro pues a mi me gusta
get along with my team and be
llevarme bien con mi equipo y estar
united, the truth is that was the only
unidos que la verdad ese fue el único
moment yesterday, which was at the beginning, which
momento ayer que fue al principio que
was the only moment that I said, we will
fue el único momento que yo dije we will
and wiwilí
y wiwilí
lio and Willy yeah  let's go from that stick there's going to
lío y willy si vamos de ese palo va a
be a weird atmosphere in the team and it
estar raro en el ambiente en el equipo y
was at the beginning I asked him I was talking
fue al principio le pregunté yo hablaba
to everyone and I asked him how he got
con todos y le pregunté que cómo se
encouraged to the tournament because I was surprised that
animó al torneo porque me sorprendió que
you were encouraged to participate in the
te animaste participar en el torneo de
OT tournament I was excited he told you they play how it
ot hacía ilusión te lo dijo juegan cómo
was
fue
but the 20 of
pero las 20
course the title of the text which is Greece makes
claro el título del texto que es grecia
Willy uncomfortable the title of the
incomoda a willy reza el título del
text says that it should be serious tries to
texto que debería ser grave intenta
talk to Greg and generate a good
hablar con greg y generar un buen
atmosphere in his team
ambiente en su equipo
uncomfortable
incómoda
this
esta
part of Willie
parte de willie
that answers which vote like yes yes I
que responda cual vote en plan sí sí
think there was a very good atmosphere throughout
creo que hubo muy buen ambiente en todo
the tournament and he was laughing it was me we have been
el torneo y estuvo riéndose estuvo yo lo
quite comfortable throughout the
hemos de bastante cómodo durante todo el
tournament we won games we did very
torneo ganamos partidas lo hicimos muy
well as a team but that moment at the
bien como equipo pero ese momento al
beginning when I was talking to my
empezar cuando estaba hablando con mi
team and well then starting the
equipo y bueno pues entablando la
conversation the good vibes which is my
conversación el buen rollo que es mi
duty to do as captain was the only
deber hacer como capitán fue el único
moment that I said will and if we go from
momento que yo dije will y si vamos de
that stick obviously the director did not comment on it
ese palo obviamente no lo comentó el
or I thought let's see that
director o yo lo pensado es que a ver
for that then do not go like that there is
que para eso entonces no vaya así hay
a person that you do not like and makes you uncomfortable
una persona que te cae mal y te incomoda
and you do not want to go with him knowing that
y no quiere ir con él sabiendo que
also I do not know how the subject was  of the
además no sé cómo iba lo del tema de los
teams I don't know why you think he was the one who
equipos no sé por qué creés era el que
chose the teams I imagine it would be some
elegía los equipos imagino que sería una
kind of draw it would be Greg's turn to be
especie de sorteo le tocaría a greg ser
some kind of leader or whatever
una especie de líder o lo que sea no se
you can't be touched you can be touched with them well do
te puede tocar te puede tocar con ellos
n't go so bad you get fouls and if we
pues no vaya tan mal te caen faltas y si
go that way it
vamos de ese palo
's weird the atmosphere in the team is
es raro el ambiente en el equipo es
terrifying but then it went quite well
terror pero luego fue bastante bien
pressure is the comment I wanted to
presiona es el comentario que quería
show you that is good it's curious but
enseñaros eso está bien es curioso pero
this one is quite woke up I have not
éste está bastante desperté esto no los
seen this Marquez the one who dictated stations
he visto márquez el que estaciones dictó
take out 25 texts in fact he admires himself he
sácame 25 textos de hecho se admira el
has done it to himself 28 guys on the subject and
él se la ha hecho 28 tipos del tema y
with 300,000 a million Paula has raised
con 300.000 un millón paula ha subido
your ceiling Willy did not want to go with the
tuya el techo willy no quería ir con el
Tigre team
equipo de tigre
out declaration of intentions total
fuera declaración de intenciones total
when he chooses it and says it's
cuando lo escoge y dice
my turn I bought it he has chosen me that he wants it
que me toca lo compré me ha elegido que
serves on team 1 with this what's
quiere sirve en el equipo 1 con esta que
happening but it doesn't matter this is the important thing what
pasa pero da igual este es el importante
William said yesterday the event that I
lo que dijo ayer william el evento que
think Grace in fact became fashionable this is
creo que grace de hecho se puso de moda
marched the first video talking about
está marchó el primer vídeo hablando de
the participants that Lopez that  I uploaded
los participantes que lópez que subía
videos that I don't know what nobody
vídeos que no lo sé lo que ya nadie
uploaded videos that I'm not going to tell anyone there
subía vídeos que no se los voy a nadie
was a video insulting frank that if a
hubo un vídeo insultando a frank que si
thousand people saw the videos then
los vídeos les veía mil personas pues de
suddenly he got like 100,000 calling him
repente se cogió como 100.000 llamándole
one-handed and I don't know what, the thing is the
manco y no sé qué o sea el rollo es el
thing if I'm not mistaken they have
rollo si no me equivoco que ellos tienen
a bad feeling about the past and they've
un mal rollo por el pasado y desde ahí
been dragging it on since then but if you tell me
lo vienen arrastrando pero si me dice tú
that it's a past like Wii
a mí que es un pasado como el de wii
Dallas today obviously you're going to have a
dallas hoy evidentemente vais a tener el
bad feeling let's go for life towards
mal rollo vamos por de por vida hacia
something like Win visiting her in
una cosa como la de win visitarla en la
life what they've done to the goddess on the
vida lo que le han hecho a la diosa por
part of Willie and the team they've
parte de willie y de equipo que han
had the messes they've had legal issues and
tenido los líos han tenido judiciales y
all the issues already with a girlfriend in the middle I don't know
todo tema ya de novia por medio no sé
what it is tremendous but these people why
qué sea tremendo pero esta gente por qué
because playing alcohol didn't he make a
porque jugando alcohol no le hizo un
video and the other one at 14 tried to
vídeo y el otro con 14 años intentó
scratch views by putting wild in the title he
rasca visitas poniendo wild el título le
told him I don't know what it is there must be something
dijo no sé que sea tiene que haber algo
here that also resembles families how am I
aquí que semeja también familias como se
running out the editor answers
me está acabando el editor contesta
with
con
him giving his opinion no such thing is the ok it's  I
él dando su opinión no tal es el vale se
feel in those videos of visits but
lo siento en esos vídeos de visitas pero
serious is not interested in your video I
grave no le interesa tu vídeo
do not want from cell to grace did not see it
no quiero de celda a grace no lo veía
nobody uploaded a video insulting stacks
nadie subió un vídeo insultando a stacks
to frank and then he also did it with me
a frank y luego también lo hizo conmigo
and since he saw that it worked
y como vio que le funcionaba tiro por
for him he shot in that direction the first thing I want to say about this is that obviously when we have been so long that each one says whatever I am not going to shut up either nothing surprises you in this world you know what I want to tell you I mean it's like it's not the end of the world
sea es en plan no es el fin del mundo
she as you know at this point when we
ella como sabéis a estas alturas cuando
have been doing this for 10 years it's
llevamos 10 años haciendo esto es
just that we don't give a damn about anything and
simplemente nos suda laporta todo y a
continue but what william jr did
continuar pero esto que hizo william jr
is as if I were reviewing the
es como si yo estoy repasando los
tournament participants and he was
participantes del torneo y él estaba
saying what each person did in
diciendo lo que hacía cada persona en
2012 in 2011 when we uploaded videos and at
2012 en 2011 cuando subimos vídeos y
the time I was starting
para que el momento yo estaba empezando
it's as if I start reviewing the
es como si yo me pongo a repasar los
participants and I say to me and william at
participantes y digo a mí ya william en
that time we were uploading apps stacks there is
aquel momento subíamos apps stacks está
the competitive game angel and saras
el juego competitivo ángel y saras
was prestiging willy rex willy rex
estaba prestigiando willy rex willy rex
is how to say it is a very good creator  but
es cómo decirlo es muy buen creador pero
nowadays you have to see what a mess she's making
hoy en día hay que verla que está liando
with the nfc she's such a rat or so this
con los nfc es tal que rata o sea este
comment would be even more
comentario todavía sería incluso más
polite because well it was created but don't you
educado porque bueno fue creado pero no
see that it's allied with the FT that rat did
ven a que está aliado con el ft que rata
not take down the family comment when
no apeaba el comentario familiar cuando
you enter a tournament in fact it
tú entras en uno torneo de hecho además
was not a multitudinous tournament like for
no era un torneo multitudinario como por
example the squid game I think there
ejemplo el del juego del calamar creo
were four teams how much
que eran cuatro equipos de cuánto
tell me the exact number please there were
decirme el número exacto porfa eran
four teams how much each team or
cuatro equipos de cuanto cada equipo o
rather four like six people 24 in
sea cuatro tipo de seis personas 24 en
total let's go 24 people you know that
total vamos 24 personas tú sabes que
those 24 people are collaborating with
esas 24 personas están colaborando con
her you know that there are going to
ella estás colaborando sabes que va
be people who play well or if I'm
haber gente que sí juega bien o si se me
good at it has grace or some kind of
da bien tiene gracia o algún tipo de
charisma that draws attention in the
carisma que llame la atención en la
game then she will gain followers of
partida pues va a ganar seguidores de
yours of course the thing with willy is as he
los tuyos claro lo de willy es como a él
grows up he was a rat that nobody saw him
crezca era una rata que no lo veía nadie
started that video enjoying it grew on me
empezó a ese vídeo disfrutando me creció
when you are collaborating with 24 people
cuando estás colaborando con 24 personas
if you have a bad vibe with someone if they are going to
si tiene un mal rollo con uno si va a
make these types of comments and it goes like
hacer este tipo de comentarios y te va
that then don't collaborate the
por así pues no colabores la
collaboration is a collaboration gave I
colaboración es una colaboración dio me
mean in  an environment in which you
refiero en un ambiente en el que tú
're remembering an era and playing a
estás recordando una época y jugando un
Modern Warfare 3 tournament for the good
torneo de modern warfare 3 por el buen
vibes what you have to do is
rollo lo que tienes que hacer es
simply generate good vibes with
simplemente generar buen rollo con la
people and apart from a decade-long thing
gente y aparte de una cosa de una década
and which I don't think we're going for what we've been
y que tampoco creo que vamos por lo que
seeing above but I
hemos estado viendo por encima pero
also don't know if
tampoco no sé si
now he shat himself in his m
ahora se [__] en su m
as if I'm reviewing the
como si yo estoy repasando los
participants and Vigo Willis Aunt Willy
participantes y vigo willis tía willy
how exciting that he's in the tournament but
que ilusión que esté en el torneo pero
what he's doing today with the NFC
que está haciendo hoy en día con los nfc
is how much hey he's falling such and
es cuánto hey le está cayendo tal no sé
such and I start like to give an opinion
qué y me pongo como a dar una opinión
on something bad you know that he has
sobre sobre algo malo sabes que haya
done with disqualifications he said
hecho con descalificativos él dijo
wow what a serious rat in the time ex
[__] que rata grave en la época ex
uploaded a video such and such the reality is
subió un vídeo tal no sé qué la realidad
that there is no need whatsoever to make a
que no hay necesidad ninguna de hacer un
bad comment about someone in a
comentario malo sobre alguien en un
tournament that we are all here to go but it was
torneo que estamos todos para ir pero
born in the context that Greg says if I
nació en el contexto que dice greg si
had wanted to make a comment
hubiera querido hacer algún comentario
on something that is being bad Greg
sobre algo que está siendo malo greg
would contain a thousand things here you have 28
contendría mil cosas aquí tenéis 28
videos about grave a month not in those that
vídeos sobre grave al mes no en los que
commented on the shits I wouldn't have said it's
comentó las cagadas no hubiera dicho es
time for the [ __ ] here about with the
tiempo para la [__] aquí sobre con los
iPods or  go [ __ ] what I did on the
ipod o vayan a [__] que hecho en el
microphone that literally [ __ ] the
micrófono que literalmente se cagan los
microphones the worst ones throw the
micrófonos los peores te tiran el
microphone at you he has not caught
micrófono no ha cogido
telling the way in which he knows
contando la manera en la que él conoce a
gres but not only the way in
gres pero no solamente la manera en la
which the colo blood but assuming that in
que el colo sangre sino dando por hecho
that way
que de esa manera
gref became known when really
gref se hizo conocido cuando realmente
serious has had being honest or rather he has had
grave ha tenido siendo honesto o sea ha
several peaks I would say that the
tenido varios picos yo diría que el
strong point of serious was the four night
punto fuerte de grave fue el four night
because it was one of the first that brought
porque fue de los primeros que trajo
form already youtube spain and strong in
forma ya youtube españa y fuerte de
fact I think he collaborated I
hecho creo que él colaboró
think that the work the form of
yo creo que el trabajo el forma de
turespaña because form and then
turespaña porque forma y luego lo
hired him I think but I would say that the
contrató creo pero yo diría que la
strong the powerful era decree that he believes
fuerte la época potente decreto que cree
comes to stardom is form is because he
sale al estrellato es forma está porque
believes I think he was in the group not
cree yo creo que estaba en el grupo no
of the shooter and these people to get the
del shooter y esta gente para sacar los
best does not have that much for pool
mejores no tiene para tanto por piscina
and played more to video games but to people
y jugaba más a videojuegos pero a gente
did not go there no the clear I do not know
no iba por allí no el claro ya no sé que
what happens that he broke it because
lo que pasa que él lo peto porque
later yes it is true that you see it and the
después sí que es verdad que tú lo ves y
best people like me people call
a la mejor gente como yo gente llaman
older to the most mature whatever more
mayor a los más maduros lo que sea más
bush see older for those that I love  there are those who
bush ver más viejos por los que amo hay
throw themselves at the microphone, you have to
que se tiran por el micrófono hay que
insult, there is that I don't know what but the
insultar hay que no sé qué pero los
kids I see a guy there who is
chavales veo a un tío ahí que le está
putting a lot of energy into the
poniendo un montón de energía a los
videos he makes and I've always
vídeos que hace y eso siempre lo he
said that I
dicho yo les pone con mucha energía
puts them with a lot of energy, I jump you see it and it transmits knowledge to the children, the kids because it drives them crazy, a good streamer, a good streamer is a good entertainer and a good communicator it rained Greg presenting the gala of his own and his father everyone throws it in his face that he did
propia y su padre todos echarle en cara
not become famous or Messi comes to
no se hizo conocido o messi viene a
mind in an interview that
cuento en una entrevista que estés
you are talking about YouTube in a talk in
hablando tu de youtube en una charla en
a podcast greater support he interviewed
un podcast mayor apoyo entrevistó a
Willy and Willy here the subject comes up and
willy y willy aquí me sale el tema y me
that comes up or for example me here with euros
sale eso o por ejemplo yo aquí con euros
when I brought up the subject give him the subject that
cuando le saqué el tema dale el tema que
I for example when I argued with
yo por ejemplo cuando me discutí con
Dallas in 2013 the one who was 18
dallas en el año 2013 el que tenía 18
years old 19 he was very young man
años 19 él era muy jovencito tío
I was already a little older but it's
yo ya era un poquito más mayor pero es
that Dallas USA for a kid damn it's
que dallas eeuu por un chaval [__] es
normal that he could be wrong or whatever of
normal que se pudiera equivocar o lo que
course but  being with him
sea claro pero estando con él
collaborating in a tournament it's like
colaborando en un torneo es como si
when I was in the squid game I
cuando yo estaba en el juego del calamar
had said to gref hey what do you
le hubiera dicho a gref oye en que te
spend your money on for an
gastas el dinero de los hay por un
uncomfortable comment that is so bad it
comentario incómodo de mal rollo genera
already generates a total bad vibe yes it's true
ya un mal rollo total sí que es verdad
that he made a joke about the
que le hizo una broma ya con lo de
strike thing well you're missing that
strike bueno te falta para ello que
the salcedo category is coming and another one had
viene la categoría del salz e otro tenía
to say okay but he has to make
que decir vale pero tiene que hacer
a lot of videos to get into the
muchos vídeos para meter categoría de
salcedo category you bastard 10 a year
salcedo cabrón 10 al año
I'll do it for you but don't give me strikes on the
yo te lo hago pero no me metas strike al
other one list the joke with the complaint
otro list la broma con lo de la denuncia
we meet club that was those
we meet club que estaba esos día
hot days it's not uncomfortable imagine in the middle
caliente no incomoda imagínate en medio
of playing when when he stops I fence and
de jugando cuando cuando se para cerco y
dance I say and dance he calls hp2 who is
baile digo y baile llama hp2 que es
carla don't be I can stand it because in that moment there
carla no sean aguanto que en ese momento
is a moment in the moment to be
hay momento en el momento para ser las
things because bad things can happen to all of us
cosas porque a todos se nos pueden sacar
and in the moment that you say
cosas malas y en el momento que tú dices
serious host serious his good video how about
grave [__] grave su bien vídeo qué tal
nobody saw it nobody saw it when I
no lo vi nadie no lo veía nadie cuando
had the biggest controversy with stacks was in
tuve la mayor polémica con stacks fue en
black ops 3 I don't know if you remember in
black ops 3 no sé si lo recordáis en
black auster it is the controversy that  there was
black auster es la polémica que hubo
now remember because most
ahora recuerda porque la mayoría de
people who know greg today
gente que conoce a greg a día de hoy
achievements or for other things that are not those of
logros o por otras cosas que no son las
2013 we have been
de las de 2013 ya llevamos unos cuantos
making my content for a few years and I had
años haciendo mi contenido y había había
worked hard to have what I
trabajado bastante para tener lo que
had but I do not like that
tenía pero no me gusta eso de que
we are in a tournament to have a good time
estemos en un torneo para pasarlo bien
ideally you release a comment like
idealmente sueltes un comentario como
roll roll a little you know the bad
como rollo rollo un poquito sabes el mal
vibes that it generates I already tell you it is as if
rollo que genera ya os digo es como si
I review the participants and I start to bring
yo repaso los participantes y me pongo a
up a bad thing about someone because I feel like it I do
sacar una cosa mala de alguien porque me
not know it is not the
sale de las pelotas no sé no es el
time to do that I think but he
momento para hacer eso yo creo pero él
made it a habit you spoke the wing michelle
lo hizo hábito hablaste el wing michelle
world bed loser then he mentions 8 then they
world cama loser luego menciona 8 luego
mentioned it is a topic that would make
mencionaron es un tema que le fuera
the consell uncomfortable he loved the turkey the one from
incomodar al consell amaba el pavo el de
pokemon whatever it was it was not a topic that
pokemon el que fuera no era un tema que
was uncomfortable for him that he was making
le fuera incómodo que estaba haciendo
videos with michu says we are
videos with michu dice estamos
insulting both it is not the same one
insultando los dos no es lo mismo una
thing is that I inside the egg the
cosa es que yo dentro del huevo el
squid would have caught grave and I gave him
calamar hubiera cogido a grave y le di
something from the strike for example but it is not
algo del strike por ejemplo pero no es
the same crazy and I would have told him about the
lo mismo alocado y le hubiera dicho lo
strike to what  I would have told him for
del strike a que le hubiera dicho por
example about iPods there are things and things there
ejemplo de los ipod hay cosas y cosas
are things that have a little bit of
hay cosas que tienen un poquito así de
a little bit of substance too it is a topic
un poquito de chicha también es tema
that has not been remembered
que no se ha quedado
later I will see it in your video
luego lo veré en tu vídeo
imagine for example that I go to
imaginaros por ejemplo que me voy para
Arroyito and I ask him I go to the FBI and I
arroyito y le pregunto me voy al fbi y
say Chihuahua he had to that they call you
le digo chihuahua tuvo que que te dicen
Chihuahua
chihuahua
the controversies not that you are the girlfriend of
las polémicas no que tú eres la novia de
not forgetting the script or the Helenos or rather
no olvidar el guión o los helenos o sea
that it makes guys uncomfortable you have to know it is
que incomode a tíos hay que saber está
in the places I do not know exactly what he
en los sitios no sé bien a lo que se
refers to because I have always treated them
refiere porque yo siempre los he tratado
with a lot of respect and admiration I
con bastante respeto y admiración yo
remember that there is a video from 9 10
recuerdo que hay un vídeo de hace 9 10
years ago that what I did in that video because
años que lo que hice en ese vídeo porque
before it was very frowned upon in the
antes estaba muy mal visto en la
Call of Duty community to abandon
comunidad de call of duty el abandonar
games it was said that I was pulling the cable
partidas se decía que tiraba del cable
that when you abandon a game and
que cuando tú abandonamos una partida y
I made a video in which I defended
yo hice un vídeo en el que defendía a
Willy Reyes and Stacks as if to say guys
willy reyes ya stacks como diciendo tíos
are YouTubers they have to take out their
son youtubers se tienen que sacar sus
games what do you care if they
partidas que más te dará ti a que
abandon a game and then the biggest
abandonen una partida y luego la mayor
controversy with Stacks when we are more
polémica con stacks cuando estamos más
piqued was in Black  ops 3 and in black
picados fue en black ops 3 y en black
ops 3 are you going to tell me that
ops 3 me vas a decir tú lo de que no te
nobody would see you so I don't know that when I spent
vería nadie tan no sé que cuando llevaba
years and years uploading videos that I had
años y años subiendo vídeos que había
done an incredible job with the
hecho una labor increíble con la
Colombian community Diana Pando
comunidad de colombia diana pando
Warfare and in black ops 3 she was already our
warfare y en black ops 3 ya fue nuestra
golden so that you in the middle of an
dorada entonces que tú en medio de un
event where you are supposed to come to have a
evento que se supone que vienes a
good time to be calm to be in a
pasártelo bien a estar tranquila estar
good mood you read my name and you have to
de buen rollo leas mi nombre y tengas
say something people 'no to that person
que soltar algo gente 'no a esa persona
just like if you get on my team you do
al igual que si te toca en mi equipo es
n't have to say any
que no tienes que soltar ningún
comments it's that just like if you
comentario es que al igual que si te
get to go with Frank just like if you
toca ir con frank al igual que si te
get to go with a person that you like more
toca ir con una persona que te cae mejor
or less it's that you put up with it it's that
o peor sea que te aguantas es que
we are here to have a good time that then
estamos para pasarlo bien que luego
Willy was my team and there was a good vibe the
willy fue mi equipo y hubo buen rollo
whole time you know what I want to
todo el rato sabes lo que te quiero
tell you but it's like don't sign up for a
decir pero es como no te apuntes a un
tournament if you're going to make comments like that
torneo si vas a soltar comentarios así
because we are not there to oil ar just like
porque no estamos ahí para aceite ar al
I can tell you that
igual que yo te puedo decir que hoy en
today what you're doing is such I don't know
día lo que estás haciendo es tal no sé
that everyone can have their opinion
que cada uno puede tener su opinión
I never thought this moment would come and I
nunca creí que llegaría este momento y
don't feel  prepared
no me siento preparado
how strong
qué fuerte
right he has
tiene la razón
literally behaved like a
literalmente se ha comportado como un
gentleman
caballero
politely I also have the feeling
educadamente tengo la sensación también
a little that maybe he answered very well
un poco de que a lo mejor contestaba de
and he didn't hesitate knowing
[__] madre y no la ha vacilado sabiendo
like him because he is very free and he can
como él porque es muy libre y te puede
destroy your life I send you an FT Bolt in
destruir la vida te mando un ft bolt en
De Soto packed that has a contribution that that
de soto petado que tiene un aporte eso
sporting a part of the
que eso sporting una parte del puente
Bridgestone Bridge in New York August 2 - alser
bridgestone de nueva york 2 ago - alser
willy red you know and a little further down
willy red saben y un poco más más abajo
he has become more respectful but in
el se ha puesto más respetuoso pero en
this in this controversy he is right from
esta en esta polémica tiene razón de
Greece
grecia
[Music]
[Música]
ah
ah